Hello, everyone.
Welcome to my talk today.
My name is Kabir Ibrahim.
I am technical lead and CTO at Prune
Payments, and today my talk is going
to be focused on the topic Riding
the AI Wave as a Fullstack Engineer.
There's there's been a shift in the
ecosystem in the past two, two years
thereabout, and a whole lot of effort
is going into developing the most
efficient way to integrate the traditional
quote-unquote, the traditional way of
use-- of developing on a day-to-day basis
and integrating AI-assisted, AI-assisted
development into it, and also agentic
agentic-assisted development into it.
The focus of this talk is going
to basically focus on how does
this fit into our day-to-day
work as a fullstack engineer?
'Cause basically the role our roles
are basically evolving and changing
as as the ecosystem is changing from
time, for as in this, in these days.
And it seems every few weeks there's
a new development or a new model
that's very interesting, or a new
tool that is going to make this part
of our work easier and make that part
of our work easier in that sense.
But how c- how do we focus on what is
going to make us efficient as as f-
as engineers, as software engineers,
that is going to make us actually
focus on the problem statement we're
trying to solve, the business problem
we're trying to solve, and how can
we integrate AI, these AI tools and
AI and agentic tools into it to just
to to make our work more efficient.
This talk is not going to be focused
on on, oh, how you are going to
develop models or train use training
data or to for ML, for machine
learning models in that sense.
But our focus is going to be entirely
on how do we use these tools on
a day-to-day basis as engineers.
So bear with me as I go on into each
of these tools and how we can actually
focus on each of them as we go along.
All right.
So moving along to the next slide.
As our focus is on our day-to-day changes,
I guess day-to-day involvement of AI
tools into our workflows and how we
are actually building things one of the
things that we'll be focused on in this
talk is going to be, is going to be on,
okay, considering we are trying to yeah.
We are trying to solve a problem
on our day-to-day as an engineer.
For example, one of the an example we
could use on this call on this on this
talk is going to be I am an engineer on my
day-to-day basis, and I am foc-- I am, I'm
challenged with solving a problem which
has to do with, let's say, add a form
that saves something on on a website, on
a web app within my organization, right?
One of the, one of the key aspects of
traditionally working on things like
this is defining the problem statement.
What are we trying to save?
Or why do we need to save
this save this save this data?
The why is going to translate into
the how, because traditionally
we want to know what kind of data
or what's the use of this data.
If it's just going to be a form where,
oh, we just save it and we're going to
be maybe exporting a PDF at the end of
the day or maybe using it for specific
problems in the future, then we might
think, okay, let's use, It would lead us
to use or define what kind-- the structure
we're going to save it in the databases.
Are we going to use
specific tables for it?
Are we going to use maybe
just store it as a JSON?
Things like that.
Now, that is how we would tend to
solve this problem traditionally
if we were focusing on if we were
writing this code and most of the
code ourselves on a day-to-day.
But one of the, one of the key aspects
that we need to recognize as engineers
now is that not only are we problem
solvers, we are also, we are also-
architect, architects
of solutions in a way.
We don't just solve the problems,
we can also architect the solution
j- 'cause we don't really have
to do some of the heavy lifting.
Of course, the heavy lifting is
still on actually thinking of the
approach to solving the problem.
But now we can actually spend our time
to, to architect such problems better.
So for on a day-to-day basis let's
say we are trying to save a f-
save save something in the database
or from a form, for example.
I… To use the tool one of the, one of
the, one of the things that we battle with
on a day-to-day now is, oh, do we just go
write the problem statements within the,
in the, in Claude or in in in Copilot to
say, "Oh, I want to save this this data.
How can… Let's do this or
do that," or, "Oh, write this
function or write that function."
But one of the things that we can
do to make this better or to even
utilize this these coding tools as
efficiently as possible, for example,
Claude or or Copilot is Providing the
context is actually very important
for these tools to sol-- to, to
solve these problems optimally.
So-- and it's our job to be able to
ensure that the the coding tools have
the right context, the right problems
that we're trying to solve before they
even go into solving the problems.
Or else one of the, one of the core
factors that people-- that we face right
now is we are moving from problem solvers
to problem debuggers in that sense.
Where, oh, an AI tool does-- uses
15 minutes to or 10 minutes to do--
so to write a particular function
or to solve a particular problem for
you, and you spend the next one hour
trying to correct it in doing what
it should be done in the first place.
So one of the aspects that we can actually
is to take a step back to actually a
few steps to make it-- to ensure that,
oh, these AI tools are actually doing
what is needed, and then they are
also solving the problem that we are
actually want to solve in that sense,
and we are using them as efficiently
as possible as full stack engineers.
And one of that is the first aspect
is to understand the code base, right?
Understanding the code base means we
underst-- in this aspe-- the engineer
understands the code base, but then
the agent or the, the coding tool also
needs to understand the code base in
terms of the, the conventions the the
architecture the, the approach to, to--
that is actually s- used within the
application in solving this problem
in, in traditionally in the code base.
And one of the, one of the ways that
can be done is we need to provide the
context to the coding tool, right?
And this has to be persistent context
most times, where your coding tool,
either Claude or c- or Copilot, you
need to provide it with context on how
your code base is structured and what
your code base is is done-- is doing.
One of the ways that we are going
to be doing that is going to be
sure… We are going to explain
a few of that in the next slides.
But then the next step it is to design
what we are trying to do, right?
In this case, we are
trying to save a form.
So that means we-- part of the context
is are we trying to, oh, write the
front-end of this or the back-end of this?
Is there, What is the, what's
the behavior we are going for?
Are we doing like an auto-save
functionality, or is it going
to be a click on sla- on save?
Or is it going to be, oh on focus save?
Problems like that, we need to design the-
the UI and as a designer problem and to
be able to provide the right context for
the AI tool that we're going to be using.
In that sense, one-- that's one of the
reason that we are using the tag, which
is find the friction before the tool that
find the problems, fi- actually identify
the solutions before even going into the
tool you're going to be solving, you're
going to be solving the problem with in
this day, in the, at the end of the day.
And after designing, you can
go into the API implement-- API
architecture itself, which is,
oh, how do we want to write this?
Are we writing-- do we want to separate
the logic into services or actually
implement most of the logic in either
the controller or the views we're using
based on the framework we're using?
Or is it something lightweight that
we can use, we need to separate
into util functions for most of the
implementations we're trying to use?
Context like that in terms of identifying
the problems that we are trying to
solve is g- is going to go a long way in
actually making these tools that we're
going to be identifying a bit later
function more efficiently in that sense.
And then the key aspect of that is
actually identifying what are the, the
passing criterias for this feature, right?
For a form that needs to save
something A core testing cri-criteria
is it needs to save, right?
At the end of the day, whatever,
at the-- after collecting all
my data needs to be saved.
So that's one testing approach.
Another testing approach is we
identify validat-validations.
We identify the validations of the data
in terms of if we have a single data.
Let's say this is a to-do list.
Do we want to-- Do we require
ki- sub ex… a description
for the particular to-do item?
Do we require either the
state, is it done or not?
Things like that.
We need to be able to identify that and
set that as testing criterias and make
the the AI tool actually understand
the testing criterias for this.
And then we should be actually we should
be prepared to review this at the end
of the day to understand what the,
what we are trying to review the work
that the AI tool is going to do for us
and what that is going to end up being
at the after actually doing the work.
And one of the questions where we
are, we should be asking ourselves is
where does the time go in that sense?
'Cause at the end of the day now if a
task that is ex-- and I'm expected to
deliver in probably four hours I should
with additional tools, I should be able to
deliver it in thirty minutes or an hour.
And where does the time that we are
actually de-- the additional time
that we are using this we are using
to solve problems, where does it go?
It has to go into actually making sure the
problem, even if it takes very little time
to solve it, it has to go into actually
solving the pro-- putting effort into
understanding how the problem is going to
be solved to ensure that, oh, the thirty
minutes that's used to solve the problem
is actually thirty minutes, and it doesn't
end up being five hours because I'm trying
to correct a few things that that has been
done wrong already from the beginning.
So we're going to go into some of these
some of these tools, and now we're going
to be approaching them in the next slide.
As part of the context of what we
have been explaining now we need to go
into actually how do we actually-- how
do we convince ourselves that we are
actually, we are being more efficient?
How do we convince ourselves in the work
we're doing and also in the quality of
work we're doing that, oh, these tools
are actually making us a bit better as
engineers, or they are making our work
more efficient as as, as in delivery,
either in the context that we're
delivering our messages in or in the
context that we're delivering in the
context that we're delivering our work in.
And one of the most important parts of
this is that we need to now understand
that we are no-- we are now… We
have a better tool to do our work.
We have tools that make our work better,
and in that sense, what are the parts
of our work that we need to understand
that these parts of our work are actually
ours, and these parts of our work are
the ones that we can actually hand over
to specific AI tools to to go ahead
and make certain decisions around them.
Now, who is the decision-maker?
That's the question here.
Am I the decision-maker?
Is the AI tool the decision-maker?
At the end of the day the, the
intelligence of these AI tools is mostly
based around the context that they are
provided with and how much they're trying
to-- they, they're able to gather enough
data to do their work more efficiently.
So it's mostly AI-assisted development
as the phrase has been coined the
past few-- the past few months.
And one of the, one of the key aspects of
it, which I love so much, is, oh, who is
the… Am I the one making the judgments
or are you the one making the judgments?
Are you the one making the
so-- the, coming up with the
solutions to the problems, right?
That is where we need to,
that's where we need to address.
And one of those things
that heavily, that's heavily
involved in this is where is-
Where do we define the judgment?
Or where do we define where our own
judgment actually comes in and where
the judgment of the AI tool comes in?
And one of the, one of the ways that
I found that are very much efficient
in using all these, these AI tools
is you need to understand that
you are transferring the workload.
You're not transferring the judgment.
You have the full context,
and you have the full picture
of how you-- of the problem.
Now you're transferring the work
involved in actually solving, invol-
w-work involved in solving the problem.
A very good analogy of this is thinking
of a, an architect and a builder, right?
The architect understands what needs
to be built, understands how he
wants to build it, and has already
designed what needs to be built.
Now, the builder goes ahead and does
what the architect needs and does what
is needed in terms of, oh, okay, there's
a pillar meant to be on this thing.
There's a… We're meant to put
a slab here and things like that.
Those are the things that the,
the builder is going to do.
And in cases where, oh, The architect
is not just going to leave the builder
to do what he wants in that sense.
He still needs to check in on the
work because I am the one that
understands what needs to be done.
It's the same thing we're going to
be, we're going to be doing here.
We need to treat the AI tool as
the one doing the work, and we are
the one who's making the judgments.
And one of the aspects we are going to do,
we are going to identify specific cases
where we can-- specific aspects of the
work that we're going to be delegating
and specific as-aspects of the work that
we are going to be owning as engineers.
And one of those things is that we
need to delegate to the AI tool to let
us know when, oh, there is there is
specific parts of the code base that
probably we need to understand better
or it needs to understand better and
probably is unfamiliar to either of us.
That kind of work is very good for
delegation to these AI tools to provide--
to be able to go through the code base and
understand, oh, what actually is happening
here or where is this being plugged into.
Explaining unfamiliar code to both, to
provide context for both the engineer
and also the AI tool is very, very--
is one of the things that is actually
good to be delegated to these AI tools.
Another one is to, for it to propose
implementations to actual ideas
that you're trying to solve, actual
problems that you're trying to solve.
This is very good for these AI tools also
to be able to they can do this, they can
do this a bit faster and it's easier to be
able to read through these proposals and
to be able to understand how-- where you--
where we come in and how we can solve
our problems together in that context.
And also just providing edge
ca- identifying edge cases.
This I found is very, it's a very,
it's very it's a very good way to
optimize the efficiency of the work
that is done especially when it comes
to debugging certain, debug debugging
after implementation and also debugging
specific features that probably there's
an issue with to understand the specific
edge cases and probably find duplications
of those edge cases around the code base.
That's something that these
tools are very good at.
So delegating this kind of work is--
physically frees up our time to make
better decisions around this thing.
So these are the kind of
things that we can delegate.
And some of the things that definitely
we en- we have to own Is we are the ones
that are going to confirm the requirements
that these tools are going to implement.
So if I delegate, based on our example
from both, I have to confirm the
requirements that, oh, my data to save
has to be validated based on these
particular fields and these particular
criterias, and I want these validations to
be done and these validations to be done.
We could extend it to identify edge
cases to my validations, but at the
end of the day, we need to confirm
this requirement to the AI tool to
understand these are what we want to do,
and this is how we want it to be done.
And then actually understanding when this
AI tool's pro-proposed implementations,
we also need to understand-- We also
need to be able to be the ones to
understand is this approach that is
proposed, does it match the current
architecture we're working with?
Does it match the current code
base or the current approach
we're taking to solving problems?
Because at the end of the day,
we are-- you, the engineer,
has to own the code base.
The AI tool is going to suggest
solutions at the end of the day, and
you have to be the ones who understand
the su-solutions that's suggested.
Does it match what the
approach we're taking?
Or is it even better?
It can even suggest a better approach
to solving this problem sometimes,
but these are some of the things
that we need to be able to own in
the code bases and understand that,
oh, this can actually be dev-- be
be transferred from one to another.
And then verifying the safety and
readiness of the implemented work that
has actually been done is one of the
things that we need to act-- we need
to own and understand that these are
some of the things that we have to
work on as also engineers and in using
these AI tools to optimize our work.
And in summary, the goal of this
is to make sure our-- the faster
that we are-- we don't move faster
without, without, without efficiency.
We need to move faster, and we
need to move smarter, and we need
to make sure our fast outputs
is still engineered correctly.
And that's how we need to use this.
That's one of the things we are going
to be looking at in the coming slides to
know how we're going to be using these AI
tools to make us faster and also make our
engineering a bit better in that sense.
We'll look at that in
the coming slides also.
One of the, one of the core problems that
we sol-- we need to solve on a day-to-day
has has evolved into there's so many-- a
myriad of tools to choose from nowadays.
And there's a, there's an inability
for engineers or to solve the problem
of the requirements of your tasks
and also to solve the problem of what
tools do I use to solve this problem?
Or what tools would-- how do I
use to tackle this particular
problem I'm trying to solve?
And this has evolved into a common
discussion around between engineers to
say, "Oh use this tool instead and use
that tool instead." But one thing that
we are trying to identify in this talk
is not… The tool is very-- is not, is
important, but the problem we're trying
to solve is meant to determine the tool
that is going to be solved, that is
going to use to solve the problem, right?
For example, the example we used in this
talk, for example, where we are trying
to save data in-- from a form, right?
A myriad of tools could be used to solve
problems on both ends of the stack.
On the f- on the front end, we are
looking at, oh, is there a tool that
can generate UI from from design for me?
Is there design for it?
Is there a UI that can generate…
Is there a tool that can generate
the UI from design for me?
What is the best tool that
can do this for me, right?
Now, on the-- in this end we can, in that
particular case, we can generally decide,
A, Corso does the best job in terms of
defining moving from design to that, i-i-
that initial bone structure of the UI.
And that's a good tool that we can
use to provide it context around
the problem we're trying to solve.
And then, A, come up with this UI for
me and how we are trying to solve it.
And also, it's also very good in
understanding the, the intricacies of
the code base it, it is dealing with
and how we actually want to solve
the problem and the code base is
dealing within and in, and in the UI.
And in cases where we are actually dealing
with the back-end changes, Cloud, Claude
does a very good job in understanding,
oh, reading the context of the files
that it's trying to… it's trying to
solve the problem and make changes or
run commands in specific context that is
needed in order to make sure the problem
is actually being solved efficiently,
faster, easier and quicker in that sense.
And basically, we are using,
choosing the tools by the particular
workflow we are working with.
And in, in editor assistance like
autocomplete code suggestion Copilot
does a very good job in that sense.
That's something we can actually
use to solve these problems in this
particular aspect of of the, of choosing
the tools that is going to be used
to solve these specific problems.
And In looking at this, oh, we are
trying to solve a problem end-to-end
of how do we actually want to
look at a way to solve a problem?
Oh, we want to save, we want to--
like a to-do list where we're-- the
to-do list we were talking about.
Now we want to understand what's the
end-to-end for creating the to-do
list is going to look like, right?
We want to be able to… The acceptance
criteria for this feature, for example,
we want to be able to create a task.
That means we need to validate the title.
We need to save for the user
that's currently logged in,
and we need to probably handle
failures elegantly and effectively.
This is a minimum criteria for the
problem that we are trying to solve
and how they, how we want to solve it.
And it helps us to understand the problem
we are going to solve-- we are trying
to solve, and then provide context to
the AI tool that is going to be, that
is going to be that is going to be used
to solve the problem in this sense.
So understanding this is a good starting
point in trying to solve the example
problem that we have in this talk.
And once we have all our acceptance
criterias in check and understand
We're-- where to start from.
Now we can now start going into how
do we provide the context to the AI
tools to solve the problem based on
this acceptance criteria that we have
already identified, and firstly come
up with suggestions on how we're going
to be solving this particular problem.
And sh- the first step to doing this,
just like in the step we talked about
earlier, was we need to pro- give the ac-
the AI tool we are going to be used we
are going to be using the, the project
brief or the context to solve the problem.
And in these kind of cases, it's--
we can for Claude, for example,
we identified Claude is very good
in understanding back-end context
and how we can solve the problem.
Claude to use Claude and to use
Claude to solve this problem, we can
create your Claude MD file and specify
specific instructions to Claude for
to do-- to, to solve s- the problem.
So f- like in this ca- in this instance,
or like we talked about, we are going
to be telling Claude, "Make sure you
follow the existing route patterns to
actually create your routes for your APIs.
Make sure you reuse UI components in
cases where these UI components are
actually going to be ch- made changes.
And ask before it adds dependencies,"
'cause that is something that AI
tools can be very, can be notorious
for in terms of just adding certain
dependencies that they feel is actually
is going to make the work better.
But in the context of the project you're
trying to solve, you don't want to
introduce dependencies that are probably
will increase the the context of the,
the, the size of the application you're
trying to build, or maybe introduce
even malicious dependencies into it
that you don't want to, you don't want
to, you don't want in your application.
And one of the, one of the most
significant, one of the best used
suggestions to your.md files to these
tools is actually make sure to ensure
they keep the changes manageable for
you to be able to understand w- how,
where the changes are being made
and be able to track the context
that we do-- the approach they are
taking to solve the problem when the
review stage is actually ongoing.
And then you need to make sure it run
tests and ty- and make sure it type
checks in cases where TypeScript and
is being used, and make sure All the
checks that could not run are being
checked in with you first before changes
are being made to run those checks.
For example, you have LinkedIn
checks, you have you have
build checks on the back end.
Before solutions are being catered for to
solve those build problems, ensure that
it checks in with you first so it doesn't
introduce-- it doesn't change parts of
the code base probably that does not
relate to the actual problem just trying
to be solved currently in that sense.
So yeah.
Yeah.
So the next aspect of of this is
actually one of the-- after defining
or trying to provide background context
through the .md files, the next part
is actually prompting the AI tool to to
carry out the task that you have for it.
And one of the, one of the core
skills that we that we need to
develop across board is how to speak
to these agents to get them to to to
implement efficiently in that sense.
And one of the things is sometimes
we are, we-- engineers are guilty of
talking to AI agents or tools like we
are making a wish to them in terms of,
"Oh, build me this," or, "Build me that."
Kudos to all the vibe coders out there in
that sense which is an aspect of things
that actually works in when-- works
when you're trying to build when you're
trying to build in specific context.
But when you're dealing with a large
code base that you need-- the, the AI
tool needs to understand this vague…
Providing a vague context, a vague
command to the AI tool is not going
to help you solve the problem faster.
It's only going to create the, create a
solution where you will likely have to
go back and forth before getting to the
actual problem that we're going to solve.
So in this case, one of the vague
examples that we could do in this case
is to, "Oh, hey, copilot, build a task
API, build a task API that collects data
and saves this in the da- in the DB."
In this case, this is vaguely
understandable for a regular tool,
but then in order to make it ensure
it matches what we actually want it to
do to minimize the maintenance that's
going to be done after the work is
done, one of the things we need to…
A better approach to do this is to,
oh, tell it, "Oh, please inspect the
existing task routes and the validations
that are currently in the code base."
Then we should plan first, just like
we under- we said earlier, plan To
create a task a create task endpoint
in this case, and provide it with
context around the validations you're
actually trying to-- you are trying
to approach and ensure that, oh, reuse
the existing dependencies and list
the files and tests that are needed.
But don't go ahead first.
Let me pr- understand or let me
validate what you're trying to work
on before you actually go ahead to
solve the problem in that sense.
So in this case, we are both on the same
page and you are we are treating the,
these tools as assistants rather than the
ones taking the-- making the decisions.
We are still taking ownership of the
actual context of the work and not
just the problem that that is actually
being solved in this particular case.
And once we can identify the requirements,
and we are okay with the changes that
are being made, for example, in this
ca- in this case now, we have said do
plan this particular approach, and then
we can even provide it with
requirements around the backend
changes that are being done.
And we can even tell it… We can go--
The more nitty-gritty you go into the
requirements, the more the more, the, the
better your chance of actually getting
a specific tool the a solution that
is actually, that is viable and that
is going to solve the problem that you
actually want solved in this con-context.
So after doing that, then we can then
go ahead to allow it to make the changes
that is being suggested when it has been
suggested, which is the verify stage.
We need to verify that, "Oh, these
suggested changes are going to work."
Then you can go ahead to actually make
those changes for us in that sense.
Then in this context, we are now going
to look at, oh, on the front end,
how are we going to use the design to
actually engineer the results, literally?
So in this case, we, the-- we are
assuming that, oh, there's a design,
there's a design part of this that
can be, that is going to be… That
we can use to to implement this.
That we need to provide the AI tool
with context to define the desi- the…
Reuse the co- existing tokens within
the application to solve, to build
out that particular that particular
implementation, and then we can go
from there to make it understand better
where to use the existing components
and the bro-- and en-ensure that
all the conventions that are already
in the code base are being actually
followed in that particular sense.
And then then we can go into
Understanding edge cases, right?
The edge cases that have
actually been been identified
in the previous requirements.
Are they suggested on our path that
we might not have provided in context?
Now, we need to be able to ensure
that we ask for suggestions.
Not only ask for suggestions, we validate
the suggestions and to validate the
ones that are actually useful for the
problem we are trying to solve, then
we can go ahead to allow the tool to
solve the problem for us in that sense.
So this ensures that we are
still controlling the context of
the problem and how we actually
want the problem to be solved.
Next, we are going to look into-- we
now have-- we have provided context.
We are looking at the solution.
We are also working with the
AI tool to suggest particular
edge cases that can be solved.
The next thing is we need to now
test the implementation, which
brings us to identifying that
the tests should challenge the
implementation of work being done.
In the days of TDD, we used to be able
to-- we it was a good convention to
write your test first, then solve, then
ensure that your code validates your
test, the test that you have actually
solved, you have actually come up with.
In this same context, ensure that the
test that has actually been written is
going to challenge the code that has
actually been generated and can-- and miss
the minimum requirements that have been
identified in the beginning of the talk
to make sure every all the requirements
are being validated and are being are
being understood seamlessly from both
parties trying to solve the problem.
And then now we are now at the point
of ensuring that the p-- the, the
solution actually matches the the,
the solution matches the requirements.
And in doing that, we need to be
able to understand the tests that
are being carried out, the debugging
that's going to be done on that test.
We need to ensure that the heavy
lifting is done by the person that
has actually written the test.
In this case, which is the AI tool,
which means all the edge cases that
have been identified, we need to ensure
that all the suggested solutions to
them match what is being suggested and
matches the requirements or, and the
existing requirements even before we
started the project to make sure we are
aligned on the problem we are trying
to solve or we are going on with the
problem that is trying to be solved.
And In that context, now
we have solved our problem.
Now we have a sol- a solution.
The three the three mantras to follow
when we have a solution to solve is
we need to validate the correctness,
the maintainability, and the safety
of the code that's been generated.
These mantras are very important in in
reviewing PRs that AI ge-- that contains
AI-generated tool, generally in, in
ensuring that any tool, any suggested
solutions actually matched what we are
try-- what is being-- what we are trying
to solve and how we want to solve it.
So to make the work more
seamless for us and make the work
more efficient in that sense.
And in that case, we solved our problem.
We've come up with a solution to the
problem, and we have a good solution
to this problem at this point.
Now, tomorrow you could go to work,
and then you're having coffee, and
your coworker says, "Oh, you just
found this AI tool that does this."
The point is the-- it's a tool.
It's not the solution.
And we need to be able to identify
that to make sure we identify the best
tools for particular solution, and we
don't just move from tools to tools.
There's alway-- there will always
be a tool to identify to solve a
specific part of the of the day-to-day
tasks that we are trying to solve.
But yes, this solves a problem, but
then we don't want to be tool chasers.
We want to be problem solvers.
And in-- it's in understanding the
workflow that we want to solve and
understanding the requirements to
solve it is going to go a long way
in ensuring we don't go from tool to
tool, place to place, and to solve
specific that we need to solve.
We have understood the context
of the importance of providing
context with these AI tools.
We have understood the the importance of
actually identifying the little changes
and the small changes to make these
changes to, to make that sure the changes
that are made are actually consistent.
And then we have identified the
importance of verifying all the changes
that have been made in this tool.
As I said, we're riding this wave.
We have to ride it to the point of
efficiency, to the point of more
consistent delivery, and in, and
most important, and ensure all
deliveries are very are more optimal.
That's it.
So thank you so much.
It's been a, it's been a good
time, and yeah, have a good day.
Bye guys.